These placeholder images would be replaced with actual product images in a real implementation.

For a fully functional site, you would need the following images:
- Hero background image (hero.jpg)
- About section image (about.jpg)
- Category images (spices.jpg, pottery.jpg, textiles.jpg)
- Product images (product1.jpg through product15.jpg)

The site will function with missing images, but for the best experience,
appropriate Ethiopian-themed images should be added to this directory.
